AD.MC.012
AbuDhabi
- Therese Honegger as a young girl. Subject also in ref51 and ref8. 10.5 x 6.3 cm, 1869; Sebah, Pascal (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Albumen Prints; Children; Constantinople; Furnishings; Girls; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Religious Crosses; Studio Photography
- Portrait of an Ottoman Prince. 10.5 x 6.3 cm, 1873; Sebah, Pascal (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Albumen Prints; Boys; Children; Constantinople; Fezes / Tarbouches; Furnishings; Hats; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- Girl standing on chair, leaning on pillow. 10.4 x 6.3 cm, 1882; Sebah, Pascal (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Albumen Prints; Children; Constantinople; Furnishings; Girls; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- Woman standing in a light-colored dress with dark lace trim. 10.5 x 6.2 cm, 1860; Sebah, Pascal (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Man with mustache wearing a fez and patterned tie. Ottoman writing in blue ink on front. 14.1 x 10.6 cm, 1912-1913; Osmanli Fotografhanesi, Skopje (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Albumen Prints; Fezes / Tarbouches; Hats; Individual Portraits; Men; Mustaches; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey
- Portrait of Miss Laura Farnham (1844-1919), principal of a school in Adapazari, Turkey from 1872-1910. 14.3 x 9.7 cm, Undated; Sebah & Joaillier, Pera, Constantinople (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Adapazari, Turkey; Embroidery; English Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Teachers; Women
- Man in three piece suit with goatee beard. 10.3 x 6.1 cm, Undated; Studio B. Kargopoulo & Foscolo, Constantinople (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Albumen Prints; Beards; Constantinople; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- Woman in lace trimmed dress, holding a hand fan, sitting on chair. 10.5 x 6.4 cm, Undated; Studio Basile Kargopoulo, Constantinople (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Albumen Prints; Constantinople; Flowers; Furnishings; Hand Fans; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- Yegane Hanim. 10.1 x 6.2 cm, 1860; Studio Basile Kargopoulo, Constantinople (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Albumen Prints; Books; Carpets; Constantinople; Flowers; Furnishings; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Jewellery; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Potted Plants; Studio Photography; Women
- Man with sidewhiskers-style beard in dark coat. 10.9 x 6.6 cm, Undated; Studio Basile Kargopoulo, Constantinople (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Woman in glasses, holding a white cloth, sitting next to a table with books. Identical to ref63. 11 x 6.7 cm, Undated; Studio Basile Kargopoulo, Constantinople (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Man with a mustache wearing a fez, holding a book. 16.9 x 11.3 cm, Undated; Studio Basile Kargopoulo, Constantinople (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Albumen Prints; Books; Constantinople; Fezes / Tarbouches; Furnishings; Hats; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Jewellery; Men; Mustaches; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- Standing man in uniform, holding gloves and a walking stick. Possibly Dr. Kirimli Aziz Bey (1840-1878). 16.6 x 10.7 cm, Undated; Abdullah Freres, Constantinople (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Albumen Prints; Canes & Walking Sticks; Constantinople; Doctors; Fezes / Tarbouches; Furnishings; Gloves; Hats; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Mustaches; Ottoman Writing; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing; Uniforms
- Soldier with a sword and gloves. 16.5 x 10.7 cm, 1884; Abdullah Freres, Constantinople (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Albumen Prints; Beards; Books; Constantinople; Embroidery; Fezes / Tarbouches; Furnishings; Hats; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Military / Soldiers; Mustaches; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Uniforms
- Man with fez and mustache with a medal pinned to his chest. 16.4 x 10.9 cm, Undated; Abdullah Freres, Constantinople (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Man with large mustache in a dark coat. 16.6 x 10.6 cm, Undated; Abdullah Freres, Constantinople (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Albumen Prints; Bow Ties; Constantinople; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Mustaches; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- Portrait of Caroline Livadari. 10.1 x 6.2 cm, 1875; Sebah, Pascal (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Albumen Prints; Constantinople; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Jewellery; Photographic Prints; Religious Crosses; Studio Photography; Women
- Man with mustache, wearing fez, standing with hand on chair. Numbers written on front. 10.5 x 6.2 cm, Undated; Sebah, Pascal (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Albumen Prints; Constantinople; Fezes / Tarbouches; French Writing; Furnishings; Hats; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Mustaches; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- Suleymaniye Mosque, Istanbul, Turkey. 18.8 x 17.1 cm, Undated; Othmar, Pferschy (Box 2)
  Architecture; Bridges; Buildings; Galata Bridge; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Mosques; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Suleymaniye Mosque
- Uchisar and Uchisar Castle, Cappadocia, Central Anatolia, Turkey. 18.1 x 23.9 cm, Circa 1950; Othmar, Pferschy (Box 2)
  Anatolia, Turkey; Architecture; Buildings; Cars; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Landscapes; Mosques; Mountains; Nevsehir, Turkey; Uchisar, Capadocia, Turkey
- Karkamis Iron Bridge (1917) passing over the Euphrates river in Karkamis, Turkey and a camel. German writing on the back. 17.9 x 24.4 cm, Undated; Othmar, Pferschy (Box 2)
  Bridges; Camels; Euphrates River; Gaziantep, Turkey; Gelatin Silver Prints; Karkamis, Gaziantep, Turkey; Landscapes; Photographic Prints
- Rumelihisari Castle, Istanbul, Turkey. 23.8 x 18 cm, Undated; Othmar, Pferschy (Box 2)
  Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Military / Soldiers; Photographic Prints; Rumelihisari; Snow
- Man with white beard and a white turban, kneeling next to a mosque window, reading the Quran. 23.8 x 18.2 cm, Undated; Othmar, Pferschy (Box 2)
  Carpets; Fezes / Tarbouches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Mosques; Photographic Prints; Praying; Religious Sites
- Sultan Ahmed Mosque, Istanbul, Turkey, street seller in the snow. 18.1 x 23.9 cm, Circa 1930; Othmar, Pferschy (Box 2)
  Architecture; Blue Mosque, Istanbul, Turkey; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Religious Sites; Snow; Streets
- Tombstones in Ahlat, Turkey. 23.8 x 16.1 cm, Undated; Othmar, Pferschy (Box 2)
  Clouds; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Mountains; Photographic Prints; Tombs; Van, Turkey
- Light fixtures, arches and windows in the interior of Suleymaniye Mosque, Istanbul, Turkey. 23.8 x 18.2 cm, Undated; Othmar, Pferschy (Box 2)
  Architecture; Carpets; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Mosques; Religious Sites; Suleymaniye Mosque
- Interior of dome in Suleymaniye Mosque, Istanbul, Turkey. 23.9 x 18.1 cm, Undated; Othmar, Pferschy (Box 2)
  Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Mosques; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Suleymaniye Mosque; Windows
- Wall of windows and mihrab with men praying in the Blue Mosque in Istanbul, Turkey. 23.8 x 18.1 cm, Undated; Othmar, Pferschy (Box 2)
  Architecture; Blue Mosque, Istanbul, Turkey; Carpets; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Photographic Prints; Praying; Religious Sites; Windows
- Boy in a sailor suit leaning on a studio prop boulder. 16.1 x 10.5 cm, Circa 1895; Studio Parnasse, Constantinople (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Albumen Prints; Books; Bow Ties; Boys; Children; Constantinople; Furnishings; Hats; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- Haldun. "Souvenir to my dear aunt" 16.1 x 10.5 cm, 31 December 1902; Studio Parnasse, Constantinople (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Albumen Prints; Books; Boys; Carpets; Children; Constantinople; Furnishings; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Ottoman Writing; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- Boy with high white collar and a flower in his lapel. 16.5 x 10.7 cm, Undated; Studio Parnasse, Constantinople (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Albumen Prints; Boys; Children; Constantinople; Flowers; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- Muhammed Sabri and Selahaddin. Two young men signed the photograph as a gift to their aunt. 23.9 x 17 cm, 1899; Studio Parnasse, Constantinople (Box 2, Folder Oversize)
  Books; Constantinople; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Ottoman Writing; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Potted Plants; Studio Photography
- Woman in dark dress with pin on collar. 16.6 x 10.7 cm, 25 December; Abdullah Freres, Constantinople (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Albumen Prints; Constantinople; English Writing; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Jewellery; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- Woman in hat with a bow on her collar holding a baby in a gown. French writing on the back, "The blessed child of the Arzuman family 1905" 18.7 x 13.7 cm, Abdullah Freres, Constantinople (Box 2)
  Albumen Prints; Children; French Writing; Hats; Individual Portraits; Photographs; Studio Photography; Women
- Albanian Girl. 20.8 x 13.5 cm, 1890; Abdullah Freres, Constantinople (Box 2)
  Albumen Prints; Constantinople; Embroidery; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Potted Plants; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing; Women
- Man and a woman standing in a wedding dress. Kemaciyan. 21.7 x 13.2 cm, Undated; Abdullah Freres, Constantinople (Box 2)
  Albumen Prints; Carpets; Constantinople; Flowers; Furnishings; Gloves; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Mustaches; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Wedding Dresses; Wedding Portraits; Wedding Veils; Women
- Man with beard wearing a fez and a dark coat sitting in a chair. Same subject as ref106. 21.4 x 13.5 cm, 1880s; Abdullah Freres, Constantinople (Box 2)
  Albumen Prints; Beards; Constantinople; Fezes / Tarbouches; Furnishings; Hats; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- Man with beard in a white suit, dark coat and a fez, sitting on a chair. Same subject as ref105. 21.5 x 13.8 cm, 1888; Abdullah Freres, Constantinople (Box 2)
  Albumen Prints; Beards; Books; Carpets; Constantinople; Fezes / Tarbouches; Furnishings; Hats; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- Soldiers with binoculars around their necks sitting on horses. 19.1 x 24.2 cm, 6 November 1918; Pokoriya, Odessa (Box 2)
  Binoculars; Fezes / Tarbouches; Flags; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hats; Horses; Landscapes; Men; Military / Soldiers; Mountains; Mustaches; Odessa, Crimea; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Trees; Turkey; Uniforms
- A porter surrounded by street dogs. 25.9 x 18.6 cm, Circa 1880; Abdullah Freres, Constantinople (Box 2)
  Beards; Cigarettes; Constantinople; Dogs; Doors; Food; French Writing; Girls; Hats; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Streets; Trees
- Two men in suits and two women wearing dresses and pearls with a small boy. 28.9 x 19.8 cm, 14 February 1930; Unknown (Box 2)
  Boys; Children; Family Portraits; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jewellery; Men; Painted Backdrops; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Women
- Bosphorus strait with views of Maiden's Tower, Ayazma Mosque, and Rum Mehmed Pasha Mosque. French Writing in the lower left-hand corner. A man in a rowboat is in the foreground. 23.2 x 31.2 cm, Undated; Berggren, Guillaume (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Albumen Prints; Architecture; Ayazma Mosque, Istanbul, Turkey; Boats; Bosphorous, Istanbul, Turkey; Buildings; French Writing; Istanbul, Turkey; Lighthouses; Maiden's Tower; Mosques; Photographic Prints; Ports; Rum Mehmed Pasha Mosque; Water
- Golden Gate and Yedikule Fortress, Istanbul, Turkey. Identical print to ref 134. 24.5 x 29.6 cm, 1898; Sebah & Joaillier, Pera, Constantinople (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Albumen Prints; Archaeological Sites; Architecture; Constantinople; French Writing; Golden Gate, Istanbul, Turkey; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints
- View of Cannon battery in a fort across the Bosphorus strait from Yoros Castle and Anadolu Kavagi, Istanbul, Turkey. French writing on front: "Vue de la batterie de Madjian Kalé et d'Anatol Kavak." 23.2 x 31.5 cm, Undated; Berggren, Guillaume (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Albumen Prints; Anatolia Poplar, Beykoz, Istanbul; Bosphorous, Istanbul, Turkey; Cannons; Castles; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Military / Soldiers; Photographic Prints; Uniforms; Water; Yoros Castle
- Grand Mosque of Bursa (Ulucami), Bursa, Turkey. 19 x 25 cm, 1880; Abdullah Freres, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Arabic Writing; Boys; Bursa, Turkey; Carpets; Fezes / Tarbouches; Fountains; Grand Mosque of Bursa; Hats; Men; Mosques; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Water; Windows
- Porte de Tripoli, Syrie. Port of Tripoli, modern day Lebanon. 20 x 26 cm, Undated; Bonfils, Felix (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Boats; Buildings; Lebanon; Mediterranean Sea; Photographic Prints; Port of Tripoli; Ports; Syria; Water
- Tomb in Eyup. Tomb of Abu Ayyub al-Ansari. Courtyard of Eyup Sultan Mosque, Istanbul, Turkey. 20 x 26 cm, 1870; Sebah, Pascal (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Eyup Sultan Mosque, Istanbul, Turkey; Eyup, Istanbul, Turkey; French Writing; Hats; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Mosques; Musical Instruments; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Streets; Trees
- View of Heybeliada from Buyukada. 20 x 26 cm, 1890; Sebah & Joaillier, Pera, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Buyukada, Istanbul, Turkey; French Writing; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Prince Islands, Istanbul, Turkey; Sea of Marmara; Seas; Trees; Water
- Mirahor Palace at Kagithane, Istanbul, Turkey. 20 x 26 cm, 1894; Sebah & Joaillier, Pera, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Architecture; Boats; Buildings; Constantinople; Kagithane, Istanbul, Turkey; Mirahor Palace, Kagithane, Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Rivers; Trees; Umbrellas
- Ottoman troops at Wadi Halfa, Sudan. 20 x 26 cm, Undated; Abdullah Freres, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Camels; Fezes / Tarbouches; Guns; Hats; Horses; Men; Military / Soldiers; North Africa; Photographic Prints; Sudan; Uniforms; Wadi Halfa, Sudan
- Friday procession to Yildiz Mosque, Yildiz Palace in the background to the left. 19 x 25 cm, 1880; Abdullah Freres, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Architecture; Besiktas, Istanbul, Turkey; Buildings; Carriages & Coaches; Constantinople; Fezes / Tarbouches; Guns; Hats; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Military / Soldiers; Mosques; Religious Sites; Yildiz Hamidiye Mosque
- Nubian warriors, "soldiers of the Khedive," awaiting the arrival of the Sultan's "Khedive" (Governor of Egypt and Sudan). 20 x 26 cm, Undated; Abdullah Freres, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Buildings; Camels; Egypt; Flags; Military / Soldiers; North Africa; Photographic Prints; Shields; Swords & Knives; Syria
- Buildings and gardens within the Fortress of Seven Towers, or the Yedikule Fortress. 20.7 x 26.7 cm, 1890; Sebah & Joaillier, Pera, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Buildings; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Yedikule Fortress, Istanbul, Turkey
- Buildings and mountains in Bursa, Turkey. 20.7 x 26.8 cm, 1894; Sebah & Joaillier, Pera, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Architecture; Buildings; Bursa, Turkey; Houses; Mountains; Photographic Prints
- Cattle in a river next to a road in Bursa, Turkey. 20.8 x26.9 cm, 1894; Sebah & Joaillier, Pera, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Animals; Boys; Bridges; Bursa, Turkey; Cattle; Children; Men; Photographic Prints; Rivers; Streets; Trees
- Tomb of Sultan Murad II in the Muradiye Complex, Bursa, Turkey. 20.8 x 26.6 cm, 1894; Sebah & Joaillier, Pera, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Boys; Bursa, Turkey; Children; Constantinople; Fountains; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Tombs
- Door of Yesil (Green) Mosque, or Mosque of Mehmed I, Bursa, Turkey. 26.7 x 20.8 cm, 1894; Sebah & Joaillier, Pera, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Arabic Writing; Architecture; Bursa, Turkey; Doors; Green Mosque, Bursa, Turkey; Men; Mosques; Photographic Prints
- Rooftops of Bursa with numerous mosques visible including the Grand Mosque of Bursa in the center-left of the image. 20.9 x 26.2 cm, 1894; Sebah & Joaillier, Pera, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Boys; Buildings; Bursa, Turkey; Fezes / Tarbouches; Grand Mosque of Bursa; Hats; Mosques; Mountains; Photographic Prints
- Countryside in Bursa, facing north from behind Hudavendigar Mosque (in the foreground.) French writing on front. 20.7 x 26.8 cm, 1894; Sebah & Joaillier, Pera, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Architecture; Bursa, Turkey; Countryside / Rural; Hudavendigar Mosque; Landscapes; Photographic Prints
- Galata Tower, Istanbul. 26.6 x 20.6 cm, 1889; Sebah & Joaillier, Pera, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Architecture; Buildings; Constantinople; Flags; Galata Tower; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Streets
- Three boys and a man standing in front of the door of Yesil (Green) Mosque, or Mosque of Mehmed I, Bursa, Turkey. 26.8 x 20.9 cm, 1894; Sebah & Joaillier, Pera, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Arabic Writing; Architecture; Boys; Bursa, Turkey; Children; Doors; Green Mosque, Bursa, Turkey; Hats; Men; Mosques; Photographic Prints
- The Golden Horn, Istanbul, taken from the Eyup Cemetery. 21 x 26.9 cm, 1900; Sebah & Joaillier, Pera, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Boats; Constantinople; Eyup, Istanbul, Turkey; Gelatin Silver Prints; Mosques; Photographic Prints; Rivers; The Golden Horn; Water
- Abide-i Hurriyet, Monument of Liberty, Sisli, Istanbul, Turkey. 26.8 x 20.8 cm, 1900; Sebah & Joaillier, Pera, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Architecture; Constantinople; Doors; Istanbul, Turkey; Memorials; Men; Monument of Liberty, Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints
- Haydarpasa Ingiliz Mezarligi (British Cemetery), Crimean War Memorial, Haidar Pasha Cemetery, Uskudar, Istanbul. 26.9 x 20.9 cm, 1900; Sebah & Joaillier, Pera, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Cemeteries; Crimean War Memorial, Uskudar, Istanbul, Turkey; Haidar Pasha Cemetery, Istanbul, Turkey; Memorials; Photographic Prints; Trees; Uskudar, Istanbul, Turkey
- Yildiz Palace, Istanbul, Turkey. 20.7 x 26.7 cm, 1900; Sebah & Joaillier, Pera, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Architecture; Buildings; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Trees; Windows; Yildiz Palace, Istanbul, Turkey
- Golden Gate, Yedikule, Istanbul. French writing on the front. Identical print to ref 111. 20.8 x 26.8 cm, 1898; Sebah & Joaillier, Pera, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Archaeological Sites; Architecture; Constantinople; French Writing; Golden Gate, Istanbul, Turkey; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Yedikule Fortress, Istanbul, Turkey
- Kucuksu Pavilion (formerly Goksu Pavilion) and the Mihrisah Valide Sultan Fountain (also Kucuksu Fountain). 19.8 x 26.5 cm, 1900; Sebah & Joaillier, Pera, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Architecture; Bosphorous, Istanbul, Turkey; Buildings; Constantinople; Fountains; Istanbul, Turkey; Kucuksu Palace; Photographic Prints; Rivers; Trees; Windows
- Entrance to the Black Sea from the Bosphorus. 20.8 x 26.8 cm, 1890; Sebah & Joaillier, Pera, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Black Sea; Bosphorous, Istanbul, Turkey; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Rivers; Seas; Water
- Galata Tower, Istanbul, Turkey. 24.6 x 18.1 cm, Circa 1900; Iranian, M. (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Architecture; Buildings; Constantinople; Flags; Galata Tower; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints
- Galata Tower, Istanbul, Turkey. 13.8 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Iranian, M. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Albumen Prints; Architecture; Buildings; Constantinople; Flags; Galata Tower; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Streets; Trees
- Woman wearing pearls and a veil with a dark shawl, holding a hand fan. 25.2 x 18.6 cm, Undated; Abdullah Freres, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Constantinople; Feathers; Hand Fans; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Jewellery; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing; Studio Photography; Women
- Woman standing in a dress, arms akimbo, with a shisha. 23.5 x 19.5 cm, Undated; Abdullah Freres, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Constantinople; Embroidery; Hats; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Jewellery; Nargiles; Photographic Prints; Smoking; Studio Photography
- Woman wearing pearls, a veil, and a dark shawl holding a hand fan trimmed with feathers. 23.8 x 18.4 cm, Circa 1880; Abdullah Freres, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Constantinople; Feathers; Furnishings; Hand Fans; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Jewellery; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing; Studio Photography; Women
- Men washing before prayer at ablution fountains at the Suleymaniye Mosque in Istanbul, Turkey. 18.5 x 25.5 cm, Circa 1890; Abdullah Freres, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Architecture; Constantinople; Fountains; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Photographic Prints; Religious Ceremony; Religious Sites; Suleymaniye Mosque
- Ceremony at Yildiz Palace, Istanbul, Turkey. 19.4 x 24.9 cm, 1898; Abdullah Freres, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Architecture; Constantinople; Flags; Hats; Istanbul, Turkey; Military / Soldiers; Photographic Prints; Streets; Uniforms; Yildiz Palace, Istanbul, Turkey
- The Battlefields of Toski, near Abu Simbel, Egypt. 20.2 x 26.3 cm, Undated; Abdullah Freres, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Deserts; Egypt; Landscapes; Mahdist War; Military / Soldiers; North Africa; Photographic Prints; Toski, Egypt; Wars
- Mihrisah Valide Sultan Fountain (also Kucuksu Fountain, Asia Freshwater Fountain), a shepherd with six sheep, and a street vendor selling food. 19.1 x 25.1 cm, Undated; Abdullah Freres, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Animals; Bosphorous, Istanbul, Turkey; Constantinople; Food; Fountains; Hats; Istanbul, Turkey; Kucuksu Palace; Men; Photographic Prints; Street Vendors; Trees; Water
- Two ferries arriving at a port on a river in Egypt. 20.1 x 26.2 cm, Undated; Abdullah Freres, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Boats; Egypt; Flags; Lakes; Nile River; Photographic Prints; Rivers; Steamboats; Water
- Steamboats traveling on the Nile River. Voyage of Sultan Abdulaziz. 20.1 x 26.2 cm, Undated; Abdullah Freres, Constantinople (Box 3)
- Walls of the Yedikule Fortress, Istanbul, Turkey. 19.5 x 25.4 cm, Circa 1880; Abdullah Freres, Constantinople (Box 3)
  Albumen Prints; Archaeological Sites; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Trees; Yedikule Fortress, Istanbul, Turkey
- Prince Yusuf Izzettin Efendi (1857-1916) as a boy, during his visit to Egypt. 10.5 x 6.3 cm, Undated; Abdullah Freres, Constantinople (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Albumen Prints; Boys; Children; Constantinople; Fezes / Tarbouches; Furnishings; Hats; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Swords & Knives; Uniforms
- Prince Mehmed Seyfeddin Efendi (1874-1927) as a young boy, standing with a sword. 16.3 x 11.2 cm, Undated; Studio B. Kargopoulo & Foscolo, Constantinople (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Albumen Prints; Boys; Carpets; Children; Constantinople; Fezes / Tarbouches; Furnishings; Hats; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Swords & Knives; Uniforms
- "Sifahiye" (hospital) doorway to the Gevher Nesibe complex, Antalya, Turkey. 18 x 12.9 cm, 1945; Tolgay, Hayri T. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Antalya, Turkey; Archaeological Sites; Architecture; Buildings; Doors; Gelatin Silver Prints; Gevher Nesibe Hospital Complex; Turkish Writing